Charles Lee Remington Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1936-2007; Series I
  - Kezerian, Stephen A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000714
  - Kimball, Charles P. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1965; 000715
  - King, Harold L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1960; 000716
  - King, James C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1953; 000717
  - Kiriakoff, Sergius G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1949-1963; 000718
  - Kirkwood, Carl W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1958; 000719
  - Kitching, Roger. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 000720
  - Klauber, Laurence M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000721
  - Klingsmith, Philip Charles Jr. Est. number items = 21-50., 1956-1978; 000722
  - Klopfer, Peter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000723
  - Klots, Alexander B. Est. number items = 21-50., 1949-1961; 000724
  - Knisley, C. Barry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1987-1989; 000725
  - Knobloch, Irving W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000726
  - Knudsen, John P. Est. number items = 11-20., 1952-1955; 000727
  - Knull, J. N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943-1948; 000728
  - Kochmer, John Patrick. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000729
  - Komai, Taku. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1954; 000730
  - Kono, Hiromichi. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000731
  - Kopp, Larry J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 000732
  - Kozhanchikoff, Igor V. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000733
  - Krivda, Walter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952-1996; 000734
  - Krombein, Karl V. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1956; 000735
  - Kubie, Lawrence S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000736
  - Kuehn, Roger. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 000737
  - Kukalova, Jarmila. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1975; 000738
  - Kurentzov, A. I. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968-1970; 000739
  - Kuwayama, Satoru. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1958; 000740
  - Kuzuya, Takeshi. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1960; 000741
  - La Due, Noel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 000742
  - La Salle, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000743
  - LaRivers, Ira. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1953; 000752
  - Labandeira, Conrad C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000744
  - Laffoon, Jean L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1962; 000745
  - Lamas, Gerardo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972-1983; 000746
  - Lamb, George. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 000747
  - Langenheim, Jean H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1982; 000748
  - Langston, Robert L. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1984; 000749
  - Lanham, Urless N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958-1959; 000750
  - Larimore, R. Weldon. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 000751
  - Larrson, Sv. G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1969; 000753
  - Larsen, Phyllis H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 000754
  - Lasker, Reuben. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1955; 000755
  - Latham, Roy. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1954; 000756
  - Lattin, J. D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000757
  - Lauck, Albert G. Est. number items = 11-20., 1941-1961; 000758
  - Lavigne, Robert J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000759
  - Lawson, P. B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945; 000760
  - Leach, William. Est. number items = 1-10., 2003; 000761
  - Leahy, Christopher W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985; 000762
  - Learned, Elmer T. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1954; 000763
  - Lebow, Richard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1959; 000764
  - Leclercq, Jean. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 000765
  - Lee, Vincent F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1978; 000766
  - Leech, Hugh B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1954; 000767
  - Leeuw, Irwin. Est. number items = 1-10., 1987; 000768
  - Legner, E. Fred. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1989; 000769
  - Lehtinen, Pekka T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1990; 000770
  - Leigh, E. G. "Bert". Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 000771
  - Lennox, Donald J. Est. number items = 50+., 1934-1968; 000772
  - Leone, Charles A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1952; 000773
  - Leonide, Mary. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000774
  - Lermond, Norman W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1915-1926; 000775
  - Lerner, I. Michael. Est. number items = 11-20., 1959-1961; 000776
  - Leussler, R. A. Est. number items = 21-50., 1936-1937; 000777
  - Levene, Howard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 000778
  - Levi, Herbert W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1955-1983; 000779
  - Levine, Richard Paul. Est. number items = 11-20., 1952-1964; 000780
  - Lewis, John R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000781
  - Lewontin, Richard C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1968; 000782
  - Leyse, Carl F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1934-1936; 000783
  - Likens, Gene E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000784
  - Lindemann, Edward. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 000785
  - Lindroth, Carl H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1961; 000786
  - Lindsey, A. W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1943-1949; 000787
  - Lindsley, Dan L. Est. number items = 11-20., 1957-1978; 000788
  - Linsdale, Jean M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1950; 000789
  - Lipovsky, Louis J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 000790
  - Litke, R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1940; 000791
  - Llano, George A. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 000792
  - Loi, Doan Tan. Est. number items = 11-20., 1962-1965; 000793
  - Long, D. B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1960; 000794
  - Longley, Glenn. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 000795
  - Lorkovic, Zdravko. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1977; 000796
  - Lowe, Herbert N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1915; 000797
  - Lucke, John B. Est. number items = 21-50., 1954-1960; 000798
  - MacArthur, Robert H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 000799
  - MacDonald, J. J. "Scotty". Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1964; 000800
  - MacLane, David T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 000801
  - MacNeill, C. Don. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1960; 000802
  - Macy, Ralph W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1955; 000803
  - Madge, Paul P. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1961; 000804
  - Maeki, Kodo. Est. number items = 21-50., 1957-1993; 000805
  - Magyar, Stephen P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000806
  - Maier, Chris Thomas. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000807
  - Makielski, Sally K. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000808
  - Makino, Sajiro. Est. number items = 11-20., 1952-1960; 000809
  - Malkin, Borys. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000810
  - Mallis, Arnold. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1962; 000811
  - Manice, Pamela. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985-1987; 000812
  - Manley, Thomas R. Est. number items = 50+., 1962-2005; 000813
  - Mant, Charles F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1920-1922; 000814
  - Manter, J. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1953; 000815
  - Manton, SM &. Mrs. J. P. Harding. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1959; 000816
  - Manwell, Reginald D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1976; 000817
  - Marr, John W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1955; 000818
  - Martin, Llyod M. Est. number items = 50+., 1936-1971; 000819
  - Martyn, E. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1962; 000820
  - Massaro, Edward J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970; 000821
  - Mather, Bryant. Est. number items = 21-50., 1951-1968; 000822
  - Matlovsky, Serge. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 000823
  - Matsuda, Ryuichi. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000824
  - Matthew, A. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1963; 000825
  - Mattoni, Rudolf H. T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1957; 000826
  - Matutu, Saleh Dg. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000827
  - May, Jack F. Est. number items = 11-20., 1933-1955; 000828
  - May, Margot. Est. number items = 21-50., 1958-1966; 000829
  - Maynard, Charles J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1921; 000830
  - Mayr, Ernst. Est. number items = 21-50., 1950-1990; 000831
  - McAlpine, Wilbur S. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1967; 000832
  - McCabe, David T. "Terry". Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1986; 000833
  - McDunnough, J. Est. number items = 21-50., 1942-1957; 000834
  - McElhose, Pauline O. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000835
  - McElvare, Rowland R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1960; 000836
  - McFarland, Noel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 000837
  - McGuffin, W. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968-1977; 000838
  - McIlroy, Malcom &. Dorothy W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000839
  - McIntosh, Robert P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970-1971; 000840
  - McKenzie, R. M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1937; 000841
  - McKittrick, F. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1962; 000842
  - McLean, James H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 000843
  - McLeod, Len. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1981; 000844
  - Mech, L. David. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000845
  - Medalie, O. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000846
  - Mehrhoff, Leslie J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985-1987; 000847
  - Meiners, Edwin P. Est. number items = 21-50., 1942-1961; 000848
  - Menke, Arnold. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1989; 000849
  - Merrill, E. D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000850
  - Merritt, James R. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1970; 000851
  - Messer, Adam Catton. Est. number items = 11-20., 1980-1994; 000852
  - Metcalf, Z. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943-1944; 000853
  - Metowski, Roanna. Est. number items = 1-10., 1983; 000854
  - Metz, C. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1956; 000855
  - Meyers, Dewey. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000856
  - Michener, Charles D. Est. number items = 11-20., 1947-1990; 000857
  - Mickel, Clarence E. Est. number items = 11-20., 1943-1946; 000858
  - Miles, Philip M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 000859
  - Miliotis, Paul S. Est. number items = 11-20., 1972-1997; 000860
  - Miller, Dwight D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1962; 000861
  - Miller, Jacqueline Y. Est. number items = 1-10., 1993; 000862
  - Miller, Kirk. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 000863
  - Miller, Lee D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1980; 000864
  - Miller, Scott E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980-1989; 000865
  - Miller, William E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956-1999; 000866
  - Milliron, H. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1967; 000867
  - Mills, Harlow B. Est. number items = 21-50., 1943-1952; 000868
  - Minor, William C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1954-1965; 000869
  - Mitchell, Thomas B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000870
  - Moeck, Arthur H. Est. number items = 11-20., 1947-1963; 000871
  - Monroe, James. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000872
  - Montalenti, G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1959; 000873
  - Monteiro, Antonia. Est. number items = 1-10., 2006; 000874
  - Monteith, Geoffrey B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976; 000875
  - Montgomery, B. Elwood. Est. number items = 1-10., 1941-1943; 000876
  - Montgomery, Steven L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1983-1984; 000877
  - Moore, Dave. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986-1988; 000878
  - Moore, John A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1960; 000879
  - Moore, Joseph C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1961; 000880
  - Moore, Thomas E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1979; 000881
  - Moratorio, Mario S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 000882
  - Morgan, E. D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000883
  - Morgan, Mary Kimball. Est. number items = 1-10., 1931; 000884
  - Morgan, William E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000885
  - Mori, James R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 000886
  - Morrell, Glenn S. Est. number items = 11-20., 1975-1985; 000887
  - Morrison, Frank O. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000888
  - Morriss, Sheldon G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000889
  - Motoviloff, Ellen. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000890
  - Moucha, Josef. Est. number items = 21-50., 1952-1963; 000891
  - Moussa, Mounir Tawfik. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000892
  - Muchmore, William B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1981; 000893
  - Muesebeck, C. F. W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1943-1951; 000894
  - Muhonen, Daniel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000895
  - Muller, Joseph. Est. number items = 21-50., 1956-1964; 000896
  - Muller, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1975-1996; 000897
  - Mungai, Michael. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986; 000898
  - Munroe, Eugene G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1949-1964; 000899
  - Munstermann, Leonard Elmer. Est. number items = 1-10., 1994; 000900
  - Murray, James. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1977; 000901
  - Nabokov, Vladimir. Est. number items = 11-20., 1946-1953; 000925
  - Nadler, Charles F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000902
  - Nagano, Christopher. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979-1988; 000903
  - Nakamura, Ichiro. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 000904
  - Nakamura, Shingo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956; 000905
  - Nathan, P. Susai. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000906
  - Neck, Raymond. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1976; 000907
  - Nekrutenko, Yuri P. Est. number items = 11-20., 1961-1968; 000908
  - Nelson, C. Riley. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000909
  - Nelson, Edward M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000910
  - Nelson, Vernon A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1983; 000911
  - Neshul, Michael. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1972; 000912
  - Nevo, Eviatar. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000913
  - Newcomer, E. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1964; 000914
  - Newgarden, Mark. Est. number items = 1-10., 1978; 000915
  - Newman, J. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000916
  - Newton, Clevland A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1933; 000917
  - Nielsen, Ebbe Schmidt. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986; 000918
  - Nielsen, Erik Tetens. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1957; 000919
  - Nielsen, M. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1955; 000920
  - Nieuwenhuis, E. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000921
  - Nieuwland, J. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1924; 000922
  - Nikitin, M. I. Est. number items = 21-50., 1957-1965; 000923
  - Nissen, Henry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956; 000924
  - Nordin, John S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000926
  - Norton, Russell. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974; 000927
  - Novitski, Edward. Est. number items = 21-50., 1956-1970; 000928
  - Nowell, Wesley R. Est. number items = 11-20., 1960-1963; 000929
  - Nuorteva, Pekka. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000930
  - Nutting, William L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1954; 000931
  - O'Bryne, Harold I. &. Olive. Est. number items = 1-10., 1936-1951; 000932
  - O'Donald, Peter. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1971; 000933
  - Oberfoell, Jim. Est. number items = 21-50., 1960-1970; 000934
  - Obraztsov, Nicholas S. Est. number items = 21-50., 1952-1962; 000935
  - Odendaal, Francois. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000936
  - Oemick, Donald. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956-1957; 000937
  - Ogasawara, Hideaki. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000938
  - Okumura, George T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1963; 000939
  - Oliver, Charles G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1966-1984; 000940
  - Olson, Boyd H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1937; 000941
  - Olson, Everett C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1954-1958; 000942
  - Openheim, Magne. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1961; 000943
  - Opler, Paul A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1982; 000944
  - Oppmann, Rod. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1961; 000945
  - Orelup, Richard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000946
  - Ortmann, A. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925; 000947
  - Osborne, Carolyn. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973-1975; 000948
  - Osborne, Melville W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1957; 000949
  - Oslar, Ernest J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1935-1937; 000950
  - Otte, Daniel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1991; 000951
  - Page, Lou Williams. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1964; 000952
  - Pallister, John C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 000953
  - Parker, D. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 000954
  - Parsons, Carl T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1958; 000955
  - Paterson, Hugh E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1969; 000956
  - Patrick, Ruth. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979-1988; 000957
  - Patterson, Donald. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 000958
  - Paulay, Gustav. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982-1984; 000959
  - Pavulaan, Harry. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986-1988; 000960
  - Pearson, Anita &. Paynie. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 000961
  - Pease, Roger W. Est. number items = 50+., 1951-1971; 000962
  - Peck, William B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965-1969; 000963
  - Peigler, Richard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971-1974; 000964
  - Pelton, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000965
  - Pena G., Luis E. Est. number items = 50+., 1951-1982; 000966
  - Pence, Roy J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000967
  - Penn, George Henry. Est. number items = 11-20., 1956-1958; 000968
  - Pennak, Robert W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1954; 000969
  - Penny, Judie. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000970
  - Peoples, Joe Webb. Est. number items = 11-20., 1960-1971; 000971
  - Pepper, James. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1948; 000972
  - Perlman, Daniel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980-1983; 000973
  - Peters, Edward M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988-1989; 000974
  - Peterson, Roger. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 000975
  - Petrunkevitch, Alexander. Est. number items = 11-20., 1940-1965; 000976
  - Pfilf, Fernc. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958-1962; 000977
  - Philip, Cornelius B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949; 000978
  - Philip, Kenelm W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1979; 000979
  - Phillips, Leonard S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1956; 000980
  - Pickford, Grace E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972-1981; 000981
  - Pierce, Naomi. Est. number items = 11-20., 1976-1996; 000982
  - Pilgrim, R. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1962; 000983
  - Pinhey, Elliot. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1962; 000984
  - Pinto, John D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000985
  - Pister, E. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986; 000986
  - Pittendrigh, C. S. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1975; 000987
  - Platt, Austin P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1984; 000988
  - Plaumann, Fritz. Est. number items = 50+., 1955-1976; 000989
  - Pletsch, Don J. Est. number items = 11-20., 1946-1987; 000990
  - Plomley, Mervyn. Est. number items = 11-20., 1938-1940; 000991
  - Plowes, Nicola Joy Raine. Est. number items = 1-10., 2001; 000992
  - Podgwaite, G. D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 000993
  - Pohl, Bruno. Est. number items = 1-10., 1931; 000994
  - Polacek, V. B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1959; 000995
  - Polhemus, John T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965-1994; 000996
  - Pollard, Glen E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1944; 000997
  - Polusny, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1955; 000998
  - Porter, James. Est. number items = 6., 1969; 002791
  - Pospisil, Leopold. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000999
  - Post, Richard L. Est. number items = 21-50., 1947-1963; 001000
  - Potter, F. Arthur. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986; 001001
  - Potts, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1933-1944; 001002
  - Povolny, Dalibor. Est. number items = 11-20., 1955-1962; 001003
  - Powell, Jerry A. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-2003; 001004
  - Powers, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 001005
  - Pratt, Harry D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1952; 001006
  - Prebble, Malcom L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 001007
  - Prescott, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979-1980; 001008
  - Preston, F. W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 001009
  - Price, Homer F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 001010
  - Price, Roger D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981-1989; 001011
  - Priestaf, Richard. Est. number items = 11-20., 1973-1982; 001012
  - Pritchard, A. Earl. Est. number items = 21-50., 1949-1958; 001013
  - Proctor, Noble. Est. number items = 1-10., 1992-1994; 001014
  - Pronin, George. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1957; 001015
  - Prout, Timothy. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 001016
  - Pupedis, Ray. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981-1989; 001017
  - Pyle, Robert Michael. Est. number items = 21-50., 1961-1995; 001018
  - Quate, Lawrence W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1959-1961; 001019
  - Quelch, C. S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1973; 001020
  - Rachootin, Sterling "Stan". Est. number items = 1-10., 1978-1995; 001021
  - Raguso, Robert A. Est. number items = 11-20., 1981-2005; 001022
  - Rapp, William F. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947-1959; 001023
  - Raven, Peter H. Est. number items = 21-50., 1967-2006; 001024
  - Rawlins, John E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984-1993; 001025
  - Rawson, George W. Est. number items = 50+., 1937-1983; 001026
  - Ray, Eugene. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946; 001027
  - Reddell, James. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969-1982; 001028
  - Reed, Charles A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1965; 001029
  - Rehn, James A. G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1951-1962; 001030
  - Reichel, Johannes. Est. number items = 21-50., 1951-1954; 001031
  - Reid, Robert H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 001032
  - Reinthal, Walfried J. Est. number items = 21-50., 1953-1963; 001033
  - Rensch, B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1957; 001034
  - Rentz, David C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973-1989; 001035
  - Rettenmeyer, Carl M. Est. number items = 11-20., 1955-1991; 001036
  - Richards, A. Glenn. Est. number items = 1-10., 1942-1950; 001037
  - Richter, Max. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 001038
  - Riedkin, Ruth. Est. number items = 1-10., 1968; 001039
  - Riley, N. D. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1972; 001040
  - Rindge, Federick H. Est. number items = 21-50., 1949-1990; 001041
  - Riotte, J. C. E. Est. number items = 11-20., 1959-1975; 001042
  - Ripley, S. Dillon. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1982; 001043
  - Ritchie, Alasdair J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1985-1986; 001044
  - Ritterbush, Paul. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1960; 001045
  - Rivard, Kathryn B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 001046
  - Rivas, J. de D. Est. number items = 21-50., 1951-1960; 001047
  - Roback, Selwyn S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 001048
  - Robbins, Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974-1983; 001049
  - Robinson, William S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 001050
  - Rodeck, Hugo G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1961; 001051
  - Roepke, Walter. Est. number items = 11-20., 1958-1961; 001052
  - Roever, Kilian. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1962; 001053
  - Rogers, W. Prescott. Est. number items = 21-50., 1936-1950; 001054
  - Rollins, Reed. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1950; 001055
  - Romer, Alfred S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1951; 001056
  - Rosen, Donn E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964-1968; 001057
  - Ross, Edward S. Est. number items = 11-20., 1947-1953; 001058
  - Ross, Herbert H. Est. number items = 21-50., 1943-1968; 001059
  - Ross, Mary H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973-1978; 001060
  - Rotger, Bernard. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956-1963; 001061
  - Roth, Louis M. Est. number items = 11-20., 1944-1968; 001062
  - Roth, Vincent D. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1981; 001063
  - Rothschild, Miriam. Est. number items = 21-50., 1959-1986; 001064
  - Rothstein, Stephen I. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972-1973; 001065
  - Rudd, Robert L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 001066
  - Rupert, Laurence R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 001067
  - Rupprecht, Jerome. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 001068
  - Russell, Loren. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979; 001069
  - Russell, Norman H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1962; 001070
  - Russell, Paul &. Sandy. Est. number items = 11-20., 1974-1996; 001071
  - Russo, G. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1996; 001072
  - Rutowski, Frank. Est. number items = 21-50., 1951-2006; 001073
  - Rutowski, Ronald L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 001074
  - Ryerson, William N. Est. number items = 11-20., 1968-1999; 001075
  - Sabrosky, Curtis W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1948-1959; 001076
  - Saitoh, Kazuo. Est. number items = 11-20., 1952-2003; 001077
  - Sakagami, Shoichi. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1984; 001078
  - Sala, Frank P. Est. number items = 50+., 1950-1990; 001079